<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>tips - Tag - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/tags/tips/</link>
        <description>tips - Tag - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:17:22 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/tags/tips/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How to Debug Garmin Crash Reports</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:17:22 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There&rsquo;s a problem. Fix it. Writing software usually comes with an element of support, this could be due to a of a lack of understanding on the user&rsquo;s part, maybe a feature is being used in a way it wasn&rsquo;t thought of during development, a user might want something specific, the developer could have introduced a bug etc etc&hellip; Regardless of the type of support request, developers need to collect the right information to be able to act appropriately.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>GIMP Colour Exchange</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/10/gimp-colour-exchange/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:45:01 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/10/gimp-colour-exchange/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Jibber Jabber Only want instructions, skip the jibber jabber&hellip;
A friend recently asked for some advice regarding some colour combinations. Below is an example of what he showed us
 I gave my thoughts, namely that light text on the light background wasn&rsquo;t a very easy to read combination and I suggested that maybe
Quote  You could do white or black text and get that &ldquo;popping&rdquo; effect on all colours.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Change Your Garmin App Settings</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:26:32 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In my time developing apps for Garmin wearables there is no doubt that the most common question I&rsquo;m asked by users is how to update the settings of an application.
There are three ways to update your apps, I&rsquo;ll detail all of them below.
1. Garmin Express   First thing&rsquo;s first, make sure you have downloaded and installed Garmin Express
  Next, connect your watch with the appropriate USB cable and wait for it to show as being connected]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>When Is a Git Repo Not a Git Repo?</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/02/when-is-a-git-repo-not-a-git-repo/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 23:12:14 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/02/when-is-a-git-repo-not-a-git-repo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I was working on a project recently and I noticed that my git gutter wasn&rsquo;t showing up in VS Code.
Quick side note, for those that don&rsquo;t know, a git gutter, diff decorator or VCS gutter is a small element that typically shows up on the side of your code files to indicate a change between your local copy of the file and that which the version control system is tracking.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
