<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/</link>
        <description>Personal blog, Garmin apps and more</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:53:08 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>How to Create Custom Card Decks With Tabletop Simulator</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/28/how-to-create-custom-decks-table-top-simulator/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 12:53:08 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/28/how-to-create-custom-decks-table-top-simulator/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[When Tabletop Simulator released in 2015, the idea of a single application that would allow me to play board games no matter where I found myself was very appealing. However, since it was a sandbox style game, unless you had others who were keen to join in the fun there was little that you could do. About a year after its release, I bought a four pack, shared the extra copies amongst friends and proceeded to play it a grand total of 30 minutes.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>CIQ Development With VSCode - The Gotchas</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/20/ciq-development-with-vscode/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 14:44:49 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/20/ciq-development-with-vscode/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Connect IQ Eclipse Plugin is dead! Long live the Connect IQ Eclipse Plugin! It has been about 5 months since Garmin held their annual developer conference, during which there was an entire breakout session for Connect IQ tools, including the all singing, all dancing, Visual Studio Code extension. Drinking the Kool-Aid, one would have thought Garmin had lowered the barrier to entry for development on the CIQ platform, in their own words]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How To Set Up a New Mac</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/14/how-to-set-up-a-new-mac/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 12:51:21 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/14/how-to-set-up-a-new-mac/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hello Mac :) Having just finished setting up my Mac for a second time in as many months, I thought it would be a good time to capture what I&rsquo;ve done to make this process a little easier the next time I&rsquo;m inevitably going to do it. You could argue that a better title for this post is &ldquo;How I Set Up New Mac&rdquo; since its usefulness is most likely limited to my future self, but I didn&rsquo;t have a &ldquo;How I&rdquo; category on this site&hellip;]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Garmin Application Unlock</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/12/03/garmin-application-unlock/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 17:21:38 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/12/03/garmin-application-unlock/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Unlocking Your Application Thank you for helping support my work with your donation. The unlock code you will receive will allow you to enjoy premium features that I&rsquo;ve added to my applications, ranging from aesthetic differences, to enhancements in the data displayed or even the functioning of the application.
Below I will outline the process of receiving an unlock code, if you are having any issues please contact me and I&rsquo;ll be sure to help sort you out.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Scaling Pixel Art with GIMP</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/09/07/gimp-scaling-pixel-art/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 10:18:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/09/07/gimp-scaling-pixel-art/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Problem I was recently commissioned to create a watch face for an individual, part of the request was to make use of some 8-bit pixel art the user provided. In itself this sounded like an easy enough task so I went about designing the watch face thinking it would be a case of dropping the graphics in place and calling it a day.
However, once I added the png I was asked to use I ended up with something similar to this]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>`ls` by time modified</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/ls-by-time-modified/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 07:20:09 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/ls-by-time-modified/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[One of the regular commands I employ when working on the command line is the ls command. A few years ago I set up a couple aliases for ls and have used them exclusively.
1 2  alias ls=&#39;ls -GF&#39; alias ll=&#39;ls -GFlah&#39;   Aliasing ls to ls -GF has given me the ability to list directory contents in colour and with some applied formatting to quickly distinguish the type of file presented.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Add Better Logging to Bash Scripts</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 10:54:30 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If I were to look for a site reliability / infrastructure / devops engineer job one of the skills that will likely be mentioned across a large number of specs would be &ldquo;scripting&rdquo;. Next to it, you&rsquo;ll likely see the word &ldquo;bash&rdquo;.
It is probably the scripting language that I&rsquo;ve used most frequently, both professionally and personally, in that time I&rsquo;ve found a few ways to make my scripts a little more robust and user friendly.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Debug Garmin Crash Reports</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:17:22 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There&rsquo;s a problem. Fix it. Writing software usually comes with an element of support, this could be due to a of a lack of understanding on the user&rsquo;s part, maybe a feature is being used in a way it wasn&rsquo;t thought of during development, a user might want something specific, the developer could have introduced a bug etc etc&hellip; Regardless of the type of support request, developers need to collect the right information to be able to act appropriately.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>SSH Too Many Authentication Failures</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:16:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Recently I have been working on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster, specifically tasked with exposing the etcd metrics endpoint to our worker nodes so that our Prometheus server can retrieve the appropriate metrics. While testing some changes to the tectonic installer, I hit an issue I&rsquo;ve never seen before
Received disconnect from XXX.XXX.XXX.XXX port 22:2: Too many authentication failures
Since my task had me inspecting both control-plane and etcd instances to ensure their unit files were being correctly executed, and the only way I could SSH onto an etcd node was via the control-plane, it was necessary to setup agent forwarding to ssh from the control-plane to the etcd node.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Prometheus Label Bookmarklet Rabbit Hole</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/28/prometheus-label-bookmarklet-rabbit-hole/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 10:39:13 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/28/prometheus-label-bookmarklet-rabbit-hole/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Following on from my previous post where I showed the bookmarklet I created to allow users to persist labels on Prometheus' targets page, I wanted to write a post explaining how I arrived at the point of the bookmarklet.
Warning  I&rsquo;m not a frontend developer and haven&rsquo;t really written javascript in a good few years, the below is just meant to showcase my approach to solving a problem rather than my prowess in making browsers do my bidding.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
