<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>garmin - Tag - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/tags/garmin/</link>
        <description>garmin - Tag - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 17:21:38 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/tags/garmin/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Garmin Application Unlock</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/11/29/garmin-application-unlock/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 17:21:38 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/11/29/garmin-application-unlock/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Unlocking Your Application Thank you for helping support my work with your donation. The unlock code you will receive will allow you to enjoy premium features that I&rsquo;ve added to my applications, ranging from aesthetic differences, to enhancements in the data displayed or even the functioning of the application.
Below I will outline the process of receiving an unlock code, if you are having any issues please contact me and I&rsquo;ll be sure to help sort you out.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Debug Garmin Crash Reports</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:17:22 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There&rsquo;s a problem. Fix it. Writing software usually comes with an element of support, this could be due to a of a lack of understanding on the user&rsquo;s part, maybe a feature is being used in a way it wasn&rsquo;t thought of during development, a user might want something specific, the developer could have introduced a bug etc etc&hellip; Regardless of the type of support request, developers need to collect the right information to be able to act appropriately.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Change Your Garmin App Settings</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:26:32 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In my time developing apps for Garmin wearables there is no doubt that the most common question I&rsquo;m asked by users is how to update the settings of an application.
There are three ways to update your apps, I&rsquo;ll detail all of them below.
1. Garmin Connect App on Your Phone   Open your Garmin Connect App on your Android or Apple device
  Make sure your watch is connected to your phone]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
