<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 10:18:40 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Scaling Pixel Art with GIMP</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/09/07/gimp-scaling-pixel-art/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 10:18:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/09/07/gimp-scaling-pixel-art/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Problem I was recently commissioned to create a watch face for an individual, part of the request was to make use of some 8-bit pixel art the user provided. In itself this sounded like an easy enough task so I went about designing the watch face thinking it would be a case of dropping the graphics in place and calling it a day.
However, once I added the png I was asked to use I ended up with something similar to this]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>`ls` by time modified</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/ls-by-time-modified/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 07:20:09 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/ls-by-time-modified/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[One of the regular commands I employ when working on the command line is the ls command. A few years ago I set up a couple aliases for ls and have used them exclusively.
1 2  alias ls=&#39;ls -GF&#39; alias ll=&#39;ls -GFlah&#39;   Aliasing ls to ls -GF has given me the ability to list directory contents in colour and with some applied formatting to quickly distinguish the type of file presented.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Add Better Logging to Bash Scripts</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 10:54:30 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If I were to look for a site reliability / infrastructure / devops engineer job one of the skills that will likely be mentioned across a large number of specs would be &ldquo;scripting&rdquo;. Next to it, you&rsquo;ll likely see the word &ldquo;bash&rdquo;.
It is probably the scripting language that I&rsquo;ve used most frequently, both professionally and personally, in that time I&rsquo;ve found a few ways to make my scripts a little more robust and user friendly.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Debug Garmin Crash Reports</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 12:17:22 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/04/how-to-debugging-garmin-crash-reports/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[There&rsquo;s a problem. Fix it. Writing software usually comes with an element of support, this could be due to a of a lack of understanding on the user&rsquo;s part, maybe a feature is being used in a way it wasn&rsquo;t thought of during development, a user might want something specific, the developer could have introduced a bug etc etc&hellip; Regardless of the type of support request, developers need to collect the right information to be able to act appropriately.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>SSH Too Many Authentication Failures</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:16:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Recently I have been working on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster, specifically tasked with exposing the etcd metrics endpoint to our worker nodes so that our Prometheus server can retrieve the appropriate metrics. While testing some changes to the tectonic installer, I hit an issue I&rsquo;ve never seen before
Received disconnect from XXX.XXX.XXX.XXX port 22:2: Too many authentication failures
Since my task had me inspecting both control-plane and etcd instances to ensure their unit files were being correctly executed, and the only way I could SSH onto an etcd node was via the control-plane, it was necessary to setup agent forwarding to ssh from the control-plane to the etcd node.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Prometheus Label Bookmarklet Rabbit Hole</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/28/prometheus-label-bookmarklet-rabbit-hole/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 10:39:13 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/28/prometheus-label-bookmarklet-rabbit-hole/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Following on from my previous post where I showed the bookmarklet I created to allow users to persist labels on Prometheus&rsquo; targets page, I wanted to write a post explaining how I arrived at the point of the bookmarklet.
Warning  I&rsquo;m not a frontend developer and haven&rsquo;t really written javascript in a good few years, the below is just meant to showcase my approach to solving a problem rather than my prowess in making browsers do my bidding.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Prometheus Label Bookmarklet</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/12/prometheus-label-bookmarklet/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 09:39:43 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/12/prometheus-label-bookmarklet/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[One of the most recent projects I&rsquo;ve been involved with at work has been the exploration of Prometheus as a metrics and monitoring tool. I expect as I spend more time with the tooling I&rsquo;ll probably be writing more posts, mostly in the &ldquo;TIL&rdquo; vain.
Today, however, is not one of those posts. Instead, I wanted to show off a few lines of code I put together which I&rsquo;ve found pretty useful when setting up our scrape configs.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>GIMP Colour Exchange</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/10/gimp-colour-exchange/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:45:01 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/10/gimp-colour-exchange/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Jibber Jabber Only want instructions, skip the jibber jabber&hellip;
A friend recently asked for some advice regarding some colour combinations. Below is an example of what he showed us
 I gave my thoughts, namely that light text on the light background wasn&rsquo;t a very easy to read combination and I suggested that maybe
Quote  You could do white or black text and get that &ldquo;popping&rdquo; effect on all colours.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Ask Questions</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/07/how-to-ask-questions/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 09:26:03 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/07/how-to-ask-questions/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Disclaimer  The below is largely taken from a similar document used at work, which itself is adapted from How To Ask Questions The Smart Way   Don&rsquo;t ask to ask Rather than asking if anyone is available to help with a problem or if anyone is knowledgeable in a certain area, state your question. Someone may not volunteer as an expert in a certain area but may still be able to help you once they see your question.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Change Your Garmin App Settings</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:26:32 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In my time developing apps for Garmin wearables there is no doubt that the most common question I&rsquo;m asked by users is how to update the settings of an application.
There are three ways to update your apps, I&rsquo;ll detail all of them below.
1. Garmin Connect App on Your Phone   Open your Garmin Connect App on your Android or Apple device
  Make sure your watch is connected to your phone]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
