<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>TIL - Category - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/categories/til/</link>
        <description>TIL - Category - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 07:20:09 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/categories/til/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>`ls` by time modified</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/til-ls-by-time-modified/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 07:20:09 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/08/30/til-ls-by-time-modified/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[One of the regular commands I employ when working on the command line is the ls command. A few years ago I set up a couple aliases for ls and have used them exclusively.
1 2  alias ls=&#39;ls -GF&#39; alias ll=&#39;ls -GFlah&#39;   Aliasing ls to ls -GF has given me the ability to list directory contents in colour and with some applied formatting to quickly distinguish the type of file presented.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>SSH Too Many Authentication Failures</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:16:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/01/ssh-too-many-authentication-failures/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Recently I have been working on our self-managed Kubernetes cluster, specifically tasked with exposing the etcd metrics endpoint to our worker nodes so that our Prometheus server can retrieve the appropriate metrics. While testing some changes to the tectonic installer, I hit an issue I&rsquo;ve never seen before
Received disconnect from XXX.XXX.XXX.XXX port 22:2: Too many authentication failures
Since my task had me inspecting both control-plane and etcd instances to ensure their unit files were being correctly executed, and the only way I could SSH onto an etcd node was via the control-plane, it was necessary to setup agent forwarding to ssh from the control-plane to the etcd node.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>When Is a Git Repo Not a Git Repo?</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/02/when-is-a-git-repo-not-a-git-repo/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 23:12:14 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/02/when-is-a-git-repo-not-a-git-repo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I was working on a project recently and I noticed that my git gutter wasn&rsquo;t showing up in VS Code.
Quick side note, for those that don&rsquo;t know, a git gutter, diff decorator or VCS gutter is a small element that typically shows up on the side of your code files to indicate a change between your local copy of the file and that which the version control system is tracking.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
