<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>How-To - Category - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</title>
        <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/categories/how-to/</link>
        <description>How-To - Category - Personal Blog, Garmin Apps and More</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 12:51:21 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.peteravdjian.com/categories/how-to/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How To Set Up a New Mac</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/14/how-to-set-up-a-new-mac/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 12:51:21 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2021/03/14/how-to-set-up-a-new-mac/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hello Mac :) Having just finished setting up my Mac for a second time in as many months, I thought it would be a good time to capture what I&rsquo;ve done to make this process a little easier the next time I&rsquo;m inevitably going to do it. You could argue that a better title for this post is &ldquo;How I Set Up New Mac&rdquo; since its usefulness is most likely limited to my future self, but I didn&rsquo;t have a &ldquo;How I&rdquo; category on this site&hellip;]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Add Better Logging to Bash Scripts</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 10:54:30 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/07/25/how-to-add-better-logging-to-bash-scripts/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If I were to look for a site reliability / infrastructure / devops engineer job one of the skills that will likely be mentioned across a large number of specs would be &ldquo;scripting&rdquo;. Next to it, you&rsquo;ll likely see the word &ldquo;bash&rdquo;.
It is probably the scripting language that I&rsquo;ve used most frequently, both professionally and personally, in that time I&rsquo;ve found a few ways to make my scripts a little more robust and user friendly.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Ask Questions</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/07/how-to-ask-questions/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 09:26:03 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/07/how-to-ask-questions/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Disclaimer  The below is largely taken from a similar document used at work, which itself is adapted from How To Ask Questions The Smart Way   Don&rsquo;t ask to ask Rather than asking if anyone is available to help with a problem or if anyone is knowledgeable in a certain area, state your question. Someone may not volunteer as an expert in a certain area but may still be able to help you once they see your question.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Change Your Garmin App Settings</title>
    <link>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:26:32 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.peteravdjian.com/posts/2020/06/04/how-to-change-your-garmin-app-settings/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[In my time developing apps for Garmin wearables there is no doubt that the most common question I&rsquo;m asked by users is how to update the settings of an application.
There are three ways to update your apps, I&rsquo;ll detail all of them below.
1. Garmin Connect App on Your Phone   Open your Garmin Connect App on your Android or Apple device
  Make sure your watch is connected to your phone]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
